Guide to the John S. Bradway Papers, 1914-1991 UA.29.02.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Papers, 1914-1949; 1
  - Court Costs and Fees in Litigation, 1934 (Box 24)
  - Necessity for Employing Attorneys, 1935 (Box 24)
  - Development of Remedial Agencies, circa 1934 (Box 24)
  - Small Claims Courts, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - Conciliation Tribunals, 1935 (Box 24)
  - Industrial Accident Commissions, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - Administrative Officials, 1933 (Box 24)
  - Legal Aid Handbook Drafts, circa 1934-1935; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Defender in Criminal Cases, 1934-1935 (Box 24)
  - 1937 Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 24)
  - Henry C. Hart, 1936 October-November (Box 24)
  - Provident Trust Company, 1935-1936 (Box 24)
  - Replies from Executive Committee on Various Matters, 1935-1936 (Box 24)
  - Executive Committee, 1935-1936; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - John S. Bradway, Personal, 1936 (Box 24)
  - John S. Bradway, Personal, 1935-1936; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - 1937 Conference Matters, 1936-1937 (Box 25)
  - 1937 Conference Matters, 1937 June-August (Box 25)
  - 1937 Conference Matters, 1937 July-November (Box 25)
  - Newsletter, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 25)
  - Haverford, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Contributing Membership, 1937 February (Box 25)
  - Bulletin #607, 1936-1937 (Box 25)
  - J.S. Bradway Auto Insurance, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Girard Trust Company, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Secretary, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Requests for Publications, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Handwritten Notes, circa 1940s (Box 25)
  - Articles, Drafts, circa 1940s; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Legislative Matters, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Mailing List, 1936, March (Box 25)
  - Social Work Techniques, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Mobilization of Human Needs, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Plans of Organization, 1936 May (Box 25)
  - Publicity, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Receipts, Bills, etc., 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Receipts, Dues, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1935-1936 (Box 25)
  - Articles by Mr. Bradway, 1948, 1948-1949; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Articles by Mr. Bradway, 1949 March-May (Box 26)
  - Handwritten Notes, circa 1940s (Box 26)
  - Handwritten Notes, circa 1940s (Box 26)
  - Outline of Trips Taken Re: Legal Aid Work, 1926-1928 (Box 26)
  - Outline of Trips Taken Re: Legal Aid Work, 1931-1934 (Box 26)
  - Claude E. Clarke, Chairman, Specified Types of Cases, 1935 January-April (Box 26)
  - Committee on Bankruptcy, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Special Committee (Poor Persons Committee), 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Small Loan Study, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Small Claims Courts, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Committees for 1934-1935, 1934 July-September (Box 26)
  - Committee on Standards, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Committee on Social Agencies, 1934 July-October (Box 26)
  - Committee on Relations with Law Schools, 1934 July (Box 26)
  - Committee on International Legal Aid 1934 July-October (Box 26)
  - Miss Ruth Miner, Committee Chairman, Internal Administration, 1935 February-April (Box 26)
  - Marguerite Gariepy, Chairman, Committee on Relations with Other Agencies, 1935 (Box 26)
  - Committee on Domestic Relations, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Committee on Registration and Certification of Social Workers, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Committee on Federal Aid, 1934-1935 (Box 26)
  - Resume of Committee Activity, 1934 (Box 26)
  - Legal Aid Society Office Regulations, 1934 (Box 26)
  - Model Ordinance, 1937 January-March (Box 26)
  - Pilling, LeRoy, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Publicity, 1937 January-March (Box 26)
  - Replies from Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Replies from Executive Committee, 1936 June-December (Box 26)
  - Replies from Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Small Debtor's Receiver, Ship Law, 1936 August-September (Box 26)
  - Social Security Board, 1936-1937 (Box 26)
  - Executive Committee, 1937 February-March (Box 26)
  - Executive Committee, 1937 January-February (Box 26)
  - Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
  - American Law Institute, 1935 May (Box 27)
  - Association of Community Chests and Councils, 1934 (Box 27)
  - Family Welfare League, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Foreign Language Information Service, 1935 February-May (Box 27)
  - International City Managers' Association, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - National Recovery Act, 1934 October-November (Box 27)
  - American Bar Association, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - National Social Work Council, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Re: Legal Aid Society Supported by Community Chests, 1934 June-July (Box 27)
  - Trips, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Material on How to Organize a Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 27)
  - Material on How to Organize a Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 27)
  - Statistics, 1933 (Box 27)
  - "The Organization of a Legal Aid Bureau" Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - "How to Organize a Legal Aid Society" Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Chapters, The Lawyer and the Public, circa 1933 (Box 27)
  - Chapters, circa 1933 (Box 27)
  - Notes on Chapters, 1933 (Box 27)
  - Footnotes to Book, "The Man in the Street and the Lawyer", 1933 (Box 27)
  - Final Draft, Chapter I, 1927 (Box 27)
  - Organization of a Legal Aid Bureau, Chapter II, 1933-1934 (Box 27)
  - Legal Aid Bureaus, A Manual of Practice, 1937 (Box 27)
  - Master Copy Chapter III, 1933-1934 (Box 27)
  - Receipts, Dues, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Secretary, circa 1937 (Box 27)
  - Secretary's Report to Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
  - Requests for Publications, 1936-1937 (Box 27)
  - Receipts, Dues, 1935-1937 (Box 27)
  - Social Work Technique, 1937 January-May (Box 27)
  - Publicity, 1932-1934 (Box 27)
  - Treasurer Pilling, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Questionnaire from Mr. Schaar on Depression, 1935 (Box 27)
  - Legal Aid Review, 1934 December (Box 27)
  - Secretary, 1933-1935 (Box 27)
  - Newsletter, 1934-1935 (Box 27)
  - Questionnaires, Installment Purchases, 1934; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1934-1935 (Box 28)
  - Receipts, Bills, etc., 1934-1935 (Box 28)
  - Legislature Matters, 1935 (Box 28)
  - Requests for Publications, 1935 (Box 28)
  - Aptitude, 1945 (Box 28)
  - American Judicature Society, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Army/Navy Material, Miscellaneous, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Association of American Law Schools, Mr. Sayre, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Association of American Law Schools, Committee on Legal Aid, 1945 September (Box 28)
  - American Association of Social Workers, 1945 October (Box 28)
  - American Bar Association Committee on Legal Aid Work, 1945 (Box 28)
  - American Judicature Society, 1947 (Box 28)
  - American Bar Association, 1947 (Box 28)
  - List of Articles and Organization, 1944-1947 (Box 28)
  - American Bar Association Journal Article, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Articles by Mr. Bradway, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Brooklyn Law Review Article, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Mark Hopkins, His Log, 1945 (Box 28)
  - "Mc", 1945 (Box 28)
  - "M", 1945 (Box 28)
  - Loan Sharkery, 1938-1939 (Box 28)
  - Material Re: Loan Sharks, 1941 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1945-1946 (Box 28)
  - Illinois State Bar Association, 1925-1933 (Box 28)
  - University of Illinois, Urbana, 1930-1931 (Box 28)
  - Rock Island, Illinois, 1928-1929 (Box 28)
  - Chicago Bar, 1929-1931 (Box 28)
  - Bloomington, Indiana, 1923-1932 (Box 28)
  - Evansville, Indiana, 1928-1933 (Box 28)
  - State Bar Speakers, 1924 March-April (Box 28)
  - Indiana, 1930-1932 (Box 28)
  - Associated Charities of Des Moines, Iowa, 1922-1929 (Box 28)
  - Cedar Rapids, Iowa Legal Aid Society, 1929-1930 (Box 28)
  - Iowa, General, 1923-1926 (Box 28)
  - Iowa City, Iowa, 1924-1930 (Box 28)
  - Waterloo, Iowa, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Iowa, General, 1932 October-November (Box 28)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1930-1932 (Box 28)
  - University of Kansas, 1926-1933 (Box 28)
  - Kansas, General, 1933 (Box 28)
  - Leavenworth, Kansas, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Wichita, Kansas, 1925 (Box 28)
  - Ottowa, Kansas, 1923, April-May (Box 28)
  - Covington, Kentucky, 1928-1930 (Box 28)
  - Kentucky Research Council, 1932-1933 (Box 28)
  - Galesburg, Illinois, 1929-1932 (Box 28)
  - Illinois Family Welfare Association, 1925 (Box 28)
  - Chicago, Illinois, 1930-1933 (Box 28)
  - Waldo Thesis, 1931 February (Box 28)
  - "E", 1937 (Box 28)
  - Pleasantville, New York, 1936-1937 (Box 28)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1930-1933 (Box 28)
  - Samuel Rubin, Baltimore, Maryland, 1922-1932 (Box 29)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1930-1932 (Box 29)
  - Alice Waldo, Manuscript and Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 29)
  - Maryland, General, 1932-1933 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, "A", 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - A.A. and W., 1937 (Box 29)
  - Addresses, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1936 October (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "B", 1937 (Box 29)
  - Bradway, John S. (Personal), 1931-1936 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "C", 1936 (Box 29)
  - Community Fund, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Crime Study Club, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "D", 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Legal Aid Clinic, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "W", 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Legal Ethics, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Legal Aid Clinic, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Legal Ethics Course Organization, 1937 March-April (Box 29)
  - Hospital Care Association General File, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Law School Bulletins, 1937 January- June (Box 29)
  - Family Law, 1932-1937 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "J", 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence "H", 1937 April-June (Box 29)
  - Horack, Dea, 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Orlando, Florida, 1928-1932 (Box 29)
  - Jacksonville Florida, 1932 April-September (Box 29)
  - Miami, Florida, 1925-1932 (Box 29)
  - West Palm Beach, Florida, 1928 January-March (Box 29)
  - Florida, General, 1931-1933 (Box 29)
  - Illinois, General, 1932 (Box 29)
  - Atlanta, Georgia, 1929-1933 (Box 29)
  - Georgia State Bar, 1926-1927 (Box 29)
  - Macon, Georgia, 1930-1932 (Box 29)
  - Savannah, Georgia, 1925-1927 (Box 29)
  - Tennessee, 1927-1928 (Box 29)
  - Illinois, 1930-1931 (Box 29)
  - Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1931 (Box 29)
  - John H. Wigmore, Northwestern University School of Law, 1929-1931 (Box 29)
  - Jewish Social Service Bureau, 1932-1933 (Box 29)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1931-1933 (Box 29)
  - Chicago Illinois Legal Aid, 1930-1933 (Box 29)
  - Criminal Courts Branch Chicago, DeWitt Wright, 1932-1933 (Box 29)
  - Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1934 (Box 29)
  - Chicago General, 1932-1933 (Box 29)
  - Bloomington, Illinois, 1928, February (Box 29)
  - Daville, Illinois, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Decatur, Illinois, 1925-1928 (Box 29)
  - Jacksonville, Legal Aid Committee of the Bar Association, 1934-1935 (Box 29)
  - Florida, General, 1934-1935 (Box 29)
  - Atlanta Legal Aid Society, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Chicago Legal Aid Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Chicago, Jewish Social Service Bureau, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Illinois, General, 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Indiana, General, 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Iowa, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Kansas, 1934 (Box 30)
  - New Orleans, Legal Aid Society, 1935 January (Box 30)
  - Maine, General, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Baltimore, Legal Aid Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 30)
  - Legal Aid Committee, Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1939 (Box 30)
  - Legal Aid Committee, Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - Legal Aid Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1943; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - NPA, 1947 (Box 30)
  - Asheville Speech, N.C. Conference for Social Service, 1947 (Box 30)
  - National Conference of Social Work, 1947 (Box 30)
  - A Convention Establishing an International Legal Aid Organization, 1945-1946 (Box 30)
  - Domestic Relations Article, 1946-1947 (Box 30)
  - A Bar Association, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - National Social Work Council, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - Legal Aid Committee, American Bar Association, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - Trips, 1938 (Box 30)
  - International Association of Industrial Accident Boards and Commissions, 1938 (Box 30)
  - Personal, 1937 (Box 30)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1938 July (Box 30)
  - Family Welfare Association, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - American Association of Personal Finance Companies, 1938-1939 (Box 30)
  - State Bars, 1938 (Box 30)
  - Community Chest Matters, 1933 January (Box 30)
  - Sacramento, California, 1929-1932 (Box 30)
  - San Francisco Legal Aid, 1931-1932 (Box 30)
  - San Francisco Legal Aid Society, 1930 (Box 30)
  - San Francisco (Box 30)
  - Long Beach, California, 1922-1932 (Box 30)
  - Questionnaire on Standards and Ideals, 1939 (Box 30)
  - Questionnaire on Standards and Ideals, 1939 (Box 31)
  - Washington D.C., General; Washington, General, 1932-1935 (Box 31)
  - Delaware, General, 1934 (Box 31)
  - Legal Aid Society, Washington D.C., 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - U.S. Children's Bureau, Dr. Emma A. Winslow, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Washington D.C., 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - American Association of Personal Finance Companies, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - San Francisco, California, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Southern California Legal Aid Clinic, 1930-1933 (Box 31)
  - General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Montreal, Canada, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Canada, General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Denver Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Bridgeport, Public Welfare, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Connecticut, General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Stratford Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Legal Aid Bureau, New Haven, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - New Haven, Connecticut, General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Los Angeles, California, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Oakland, California, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - U.S. Children's Bureau, 1935-1936 (Box 31)
  - Washington, General, 1935-1936 (Box 31)
  - Berkeley, California, 1935 (Box 31)
  - Los Angeles, Legal Aid Clinic, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Los Angeles, General, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Montreal Legal Aid Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Canada, General, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Denver Legal Aid Society, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Delaware, General, 1934, July (Box 31)
  - U.S. Children's Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Washington Legal Aid Bureau, 1934-1935 (Box 31)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1947 (Box 31)
  - "R", 1947 (Box 31)
  - Committee Chairman, 1931 October-December (Box 31)
  - Chicago Meeting of Family Welfare Association and National Association, 1931-1932 (Box 31)
  - Committee, 1932-1933 (Box 31)
  - Philadelphia, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - William N. Ottinger, Philadelphia, 1934 (Box 31)
  - Pennsylvania, General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Memphis, Tennessee, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Dallas, Texas, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Madison, Wisconsin, 1934, March (Box 31)
  - Texas, General, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Salt Lake City, Utah, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Seattle, Washington, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Charleston, West Virginia, 1933 (Box 31)
  - West Virginia, General, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Wheeling, West Virginia, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
  - American Association of Personal Finance Companies, 1937-1938 (Box 31)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1931-1932 (Box 31)
  - Form Letters, 1931-1932 (Box 31)
  - "Lawyer's Duty to Clients without Funds," Cleveland Bar Journal, 1931 (Box 31)
  - Material to be Printed for Buffalo Convention, 1931 (Box 31)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1932-1933 (Box 31)
  - Treasurer, Mr. Pilling, 1931-1933 (Box 32)
  - Philadelphia Meeting, National Conference of Social Work and National Association, 1932 (Box 32)
  - Miss McHale, 1931 (Box 32)
  - Committee Preference, 1931 (Box 32)
  - Materials for Binding, 1930 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1929-1932 (Box 32)
  - Papers Re: State-Wide Development of Legal Aid Organizations, 1929-1932 (Box 32)
  - Re: Questionnaires at Conventions, 1932 (Box 32)
  - Receipts, 1931-1932 (Box 32)
  - Reno Divorce, 1932 (Box 32)
  - Reports of Committees, 1932 (Box 32)
  - Unemployment Relief Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 32)
  - Round Table for Legal Aid Clinics, 1932-1933 (Box 32)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1937-1938 (Box 32)
  - American Association of Social Workers, 1937-1938 (Box 32)
  - American Bar Association Survey, General, 1937-1938 (Box 32)
  - American Association of Schools of Social Work, 1937, December (Box 32)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1937 (Box 32)
  - Family Welfare Association, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Foreign Language Information Service, 1938 (Box 32)
  - National Conference on Social Work, 1937-1938 (Box 32)
  - National Social Work Council, 1937-1938 (Box 32)
  - Legal Aid Society of Pittsburgh, 1933-1934 (Box 32)
  - Philadelphia Legal Aid Bureau, 1934 (Box 32)
  - Voluntary Defender Committee, Philadelphia Pennsylvania, 1935 (Box 32)
  - M.W. Acheson, Jr., 1934-1935 (Box 32)
  - Philadelphia, General, 1934-1935 (Box 32)
  - Tennessee, General, 1935 March (Box 32)
  - Free Legal Aid Bureau, 1934 (Box 32)
  - Salt Lake City Legal Aid Society, 1935 (Box 32)
  - Richmond Department of Welfare, 1934-1935 (Box 32)
  - Seattle, 1934 (Box 32)
  - West Virginia, General, 1934 November (Box 32)
  - Milwaukee, Legal Aid Society, 1934-1935 (Box 32)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1935 (Box 32)
  - Detailed Statistics, 1932-1933 (Box 32)
  - Executive Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 32)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1933-1934 (Box 32)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Re: Philadelphia Legal Aid Society, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania State Bar, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - American Bar Association, 1937-1938; 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Trips, 1937 (Box 33)
  - World's Fair Committee, 1938 January (Box 33)
  - Publicity and Finance, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Relations with Law Schools, 1938 March-April (Box 33)
  - Committee on Bar Organization Activities, 1938 March-June (Box 33)
  - Nominating Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Legal Education and Admissions to Bar (AB), 1938 May-June (Box 33)
  - On Relations with Other Agencies, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Correspondence with Evans, Chairman of the Committee on Credentials and Admissions of A.B.A., 1938 (Box 33)
  - Internal Administration, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Contacting A.B. People in Washington D.C., 1938 (Box 33)
  - Specified Types of Cases, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Public Administration Service, 1937-1938 (Box 33)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1938 (Box 33)
  - American Bar Association, 1936-1937 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Publicity, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Small Loans and Investments, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Relations with Law Schools, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on International Legal Aid Work, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Relations with the Bar, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Relations with Social Agencies, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee on Standards, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Various State Bar Association, 1938 (Box 33)
  - Drafts, circa 1930-1945 (Box 33)
  - Statistics from Children's Bureau, 1932 (Box 33)
  - Second Sheets, 1934 (Box 33)
  - Convention Suggestions, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Committee Reports, 1933-1934 (Box 33)
  - Convention, 1933-1934 (Box 34)
  - Detailed Statistics, 1932-1933 (Box 34)
  - LeRoy Pilling, Treasurer, 1935-1936 (Box 34)
  - Re: Good Will Court, 1935-1936 (Box 34)
  - "Lance of Justice", 1935-1936 (Box 34)
  - Legal Aid Progress, 1935-1936 (Box 34)
  - Minimum Statistics, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Finances, 1932-1936 (Box 34)
  - Form Letters, 1935-1936; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Officers, 1935 October-November (Box 34)
  - Correspondence between Mr. Bradway and Grace P. Maness, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous Statistics, 1936 (Box 34)
  - Detailed Statistics, 1935-1936; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Inquiries, 1935-1936 (Box 34)
  - State Bar Legal Aid Committees, 1937-1938 (Box 34)
  - State Bar Legal Aid Committee, 1937 (Box 34)
  - Treasurer Pilling, 1933-1934 (Box 34)
  - Washington State Survey Report, 1938-1939; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Mr. Summers' Bill in Washington, 1939 (Box 34)
  - Cincinnati, 1939-1940 (Box 34)
  - American Bar Association, 1933-1934 (Box 34)
  - Minutes, Executive Committee, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Re: Surveys, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Community Chests and Councils, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Loan Shark Problem in Dallas, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Community on Procedure, Prosecution, and Defense; Judge W. McKay Skillman, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence, Reginald Heber Smith, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Contributions, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Wilbur L. Gray, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Henry C. Hart, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - American Bar Association Conference, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - National Association of Legal Aid Organizations Secretary's Report, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Philadelphia Situation, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Philadelphia Situation, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Edmund Beckwith, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Receipts, Dues, 1938-1939; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Legal Aid Progress, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Honorable E. Fabre Surveyor, 1939 February (Box 35)
  - Jacksonville Problem, 1938 (Box 35)
  - Newsletter, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Officers, 1938 (Box 35)
  - LeRoy G. Pilling, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Executive Committee, 1939 (Box 35)
  - LeRoy G. Pilling, 1939-1940 (Box 35)
  - New Bureaus, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Officers (1941), 1940 November (Box 35)
  - Officers, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Receipts, Bills, 1940-1941 (Box 35)
  - Newsletter, 1939-1940 (Box 35)
  - Paid Assigned Counsel System, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Mr. Economos, Illinois Survey, 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - Beckwiths' Survey, New York City, 1938-1940 (Box 35)
  - Bulletin #607, 1939 June (Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1940 (Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1939-1940 (Box 35)
  - Secretary, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Social Work Techniques, 1939-1940 (Box 36)
  - Inter-Society Relationship, 1939 October-November (Box 36)
  - Proceedings of Grand Rapids Conference, 1939; 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 1939 Conference, Grand Rapids, 3 folders (Box 36)
  - Correspondence Regarding, "The Work of Legal Aid Committees of the Bar Association, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence Regarding, "The Work of Legal Aid Committees of the Bar Association, 1938 (Box 36)
  - Stewarts' Surveys, Pennsylvania, 1938-1939 (Box 36)
  - Clephane's Survey, Washington DC, 1938-1939 (Box 36)
  - Theophilus Surveys, Pennsylvania, 1938-1939 (Box 36)
  - Project Cards, circa 1940s (Box 36)
  - Form Letters, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Form Letters, 1938-1939 (Box 36)
  - North Carolina Survey, 1939 (Box 36)
  - Reports, 1940 (Box 36)
  - Report from the United States of America to the League of Nations: "Questions Related to Legal Aid for the Poor", 1924; 3 folders (Box 36)
    Scope and Contents
    Prepared by NALAO.
  - "Footprints" Legal Aid Clinic at Duke University newsclippings, 1931-1935
- Volumes, 1922-1934
  This series includes correspondence, research documents, pamplets, court cases, and other materials which have been bound together into volumes. There are three separate series of volumes, which were numbered, and all of which are incomplete.
  NALAO documents consist of pamphlets, reports, correspondence, and other documents relating to the formation, activities, and committees of the National Association of Legal Aid Organizations (NALAO).
  Ellis Estate volumes consist of court documents, correspondence, research materials, and other materials related to the 1920s court case of the Charles R. Ellis trust established to create the Ellis School for Fatherless Girls and aid societies contesting the terms of the will that established the trust. This collection includes volumes 3, 5, and 6, while volumes 1, 2, and 4 are held at the Duke University Law Library. Catalog record for these volumes here.